NYSUT Publications 6174 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 2, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: NYSUT Leader, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.26:no. 2 (2007:Sept. 7)
  - Item 6: NYSUT Leader, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.26:no. 3 (2007:Sept. 21)
  - Item 7: NYSUT Leader, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25:no.9 (2007:Jan. 5)
  - Item 8: NYSUT Leader, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25:no.10 (2007:Jan. 19)
  - Item 9: NYSUT Leader, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25:no.11 (2007:Feb. 2)
  - Item 10: NYSUT Leader, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25:no.12 (2007:Feb. 16)
  - Item 11: NYSUT Leader, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25:no.13 (2007:Mar. 2)
  - Item 12: NYSUT Leader, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25:no.14 (2007:Mar. 16)
  - Item 13: NYSUT Leader, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25:no.15 (2007:Mar. 30)
  - Item 14: NYSUT Leader, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25:no.16 (2007:Apr. 13)
  - Item 15: NYSUT Leader, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25:no.17 (2007:May 11)
  - Item 16: NYSUT Leader, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25:no.18 (2007:May 25)
  - Item 17: NYSUT Leader, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.1 (2003:Aug. 29)
  - Item 18: NYSUT Leader, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.2 (2003:Sept. 12)
  - Item 19: NYSUT Leader, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.3 (2003:Sept. 26)
  - Item 20: NYSUT Leader, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.4 (2003:Oct. 10)
  - Item 21: NYSUT Leader, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.5 (2003:Oct. 24)
  - Item 22: NYSUT Leader, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.6 (2003:Nov. 7)
  - Item 23: NYSUT Leader, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.7 (2003:Nov. 21)
  - Item 24: NYSUT Leader, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.8 (2003:Dec. 5)
  - Item 25: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.9 (2004:Jan. 2)
  - Item 26: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.10 (2004:Jan. 16)
  - Item 27: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.11 (2004:Jan. 30)
  - Item 28: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.12 (2004:Feb. 13)
  - Item 29: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.13 (2004:Feb. 27)
  - Item 30: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.14 (2004:Mar. 12)
  - Item 31: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.5 (2004:Oct. 22)
  - Item 32: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.6 (2004:Nov. 1)
  - Item 33: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.7 (2004:Nov. 5)
  - Item 34: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.8 (2004:Nov.19)
  - Item 35: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.9 (2004:Dec. 3)
  - Item 36: NYSUT Leader, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.10 (2005:Jan. 7)
  - Item 37: NYSUT Leader, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.11 (2005:Jan. 21)
  - Item 38: NYSUT Leader, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.12 (2005:Feb. 4)
  - Item 39: NYSUT Leader, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.13 (2005:Feb. 18)
  - Item 40: NYSUT Leader, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.14 (2005:Mar. 4)
  - Item 41: NYSUT Leader, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.15 (2005:Mar. 18)
  - Item 42: NYSUT Leader, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 43: NYSUT Leader, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.16 (2005:Apr. 1)
  - Item 44: NYSUT Leader, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.17 (2005:Apr. 29)
  - Item 45: NYSUT Leader, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.18 (2005:May 13)
  - Item 46: NYSUT Leader, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.19 (2005:May 27)
  - Item 47: NYSUT Leader, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.20 (2005:June 17)
  - Item 48: NYSUT Leader, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24:no.1 (2005:Aug. 26)
  - Item 49: NYSUT Leader, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24:no.2 (2005:Sept. 9)
  - Item 50: NYSUT Leader, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24:no.3 (2005:Sept. 23)
  - Item 51: NYSUT Leader, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24:no.4 (2005:Oct. 7)
  - Item 52: NYSUT Leader, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24:no.5 (2005:Oct. 21)
  - Item 53: NYSUT Leader, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24:no.6 (2005:Nov. 4)
  - Item 54: NYSUT Leader, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24:no.7 (2005:Nov. 18)
  - Item 55: NYSUT Leader, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24:no.8 (2005:Dec. 9)
  - Item 56: NYSUT Leader, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24:no.9 (2006:Jan. 2)
  - Item 57: NYSUT Leader, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24:no.10 (2006:Jan. 20)
  - Item 58: NYSUT Leader, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24:no.12 (2006:Feb. 17)
  - Item 59: NYSUT Leader, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24:no.13 (2006:Mar. 3)
  - Item 60: NYSUT Leader, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24:no.14 (2006:Mar. 17)
  - Item 61: NYSUT Leader, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24:no.15 (2006:Mar. 31)
  - Item 62: NYSUT Leader, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24:no.16 (2006:Apr. 14)
  - Item 63: NYSUT Leader, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24:no.17 (2006:Apr. 28)
  - Item 64: NYSUT Leader, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24:no.19 (2006:May 26)
  - Item 65: NYSUT Leader, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24:no.20 (2006:June 9)
  - Item 66: NYSUT Leader, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24:no.21 (2006:June 16)
  - Item 67: NYSUT Leader, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25:no.1 (2006:Aug. 25)
  - Item 68: NYSUT Leader, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25:no.2 (2006:Sept. 8)
  - Item 69: NYSUT Leader, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25:no.3 (2006:Sept. 22)
  - Item 70: NYSUT Leader, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25:no.4 (2006:Oct. 6)
  - Item 71: NYSUT Leader, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25:no.5 (2006:Oct. 20)
  - Item 72: NYSUT Leader, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25:no.6 (2006:Nov. 3)
  - Item 73: NYSUT Leader, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25:no.7 (2006:Nov. 17)
  - Item 74: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.15 (2004:Apr. 2)
  - Item 75: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.16 (2004:Apr. 9)
  - Item 76: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.17 (2004:Apr. 23)
  - Item 77: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.18 (2004:May 7)
  - Item 78: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.19 (2004:May 21)
  - Item 79: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.19 (2004:May 21). Copy 2.
  - Item 80: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.20 (2004:June 4)
  - Item 81: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.22:no.21 (2004:June 30)
  - Item 82: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.1 (2004:Aug. 27)
  - Item 83: NYSUT Leader, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.4 (2004:Oct. 8)
- Box: 2, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Preventive Law Guide, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.66 (2005:May)
  - Item 2: Preventive Law Guide, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67 (2005:Sept.)
  - Item 3: Preventive Law Guide, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.68 (2006:Jan.)
  - Item 4: Preventive Law Guide, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.70 (2006:Sept.)
  - Item 5: Preventive Law Guide, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71 (2007:Jan.)
  - Item 6: Preventive Law Guide, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.72 (2007:May)
  - Item 7: Preventive Law Guide, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.73 (2007:Sept.)
- Box: 2, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: RA Reporter, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: May 6, 2006.
  - Item 2: RA Reporter, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: April 28, 2007.
- Box: 2, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Retiree Organizer, 2001; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.13:no.11 (2001:July/Aug.)
  - Item 2: Retiree Organizer, 2001; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.14:no.1 (2001:Sept.)
  - Item 3: Retiree Organizer, 2001; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.14:no.2 (2001:Oct.)
  - Item 4: Retiree Organizer, 2001; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.14:no.3 (2001:Nov.)
  - Item 5: Retiree Organizer, 2001; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.14:no.4 (2001:Dec.)
  - Item 6: Retiree Organizer, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.14:no.5 (2002:Jan.)
  - Item 7: Retiree Organizer, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.14:no.6 (2002:Feb.)
  - Item 8: Retiree Organizer, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.14:no.7 (2002:Mar.)
  - Item 9: Retiree Organizer, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.14:no.8 (2002:Apr.)
  - Item 10: Retiree Organizer, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.14:no.9 (2002:May)
  - Item 11: Retiree Organizer, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.21:no.1 (2007:Sept.)
  - Item 12: Retiree Organizer, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.21:no.1 (2007:Sept.). Copy 2.
  - Item 13: Retiree Organizer, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.21:no.2 (2007:Oct.)
  - Item 14: Retiree Organizer, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.21:no.3 (2007:Nov.)
  - Item 15: Retiree Organizer, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.21:no.4 (2007:Dec.)
  - Item 16: Retiree Organizer, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.21:no.5 (2008:Jan.)
  - Item 17: Retiree Organizer, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.21:no.6 (2008:Feb.)
  - Item 18: Retiree Organizer, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.21:no.7 (2008:Mar.)
  - Item 19: Retiree Organizer, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.21:no.8 (2008:Apr.)
  - Item 20: Retiree Organizer, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.21:no.9 (2008:May.)
  - Item 21: Retiree Organizer, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.21:no.10 (2008:June)
  - Item 22: Retiree Organizer, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.22:no.1 (2008:Sept.)
  - Item 23: Retiree Organizer, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.22:no.3 (2008:Nov./Dec.)
  - Item 24: Retiree Organizer, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.22:no.4 (2009:Jan.)
  - Item 25: Retiree Organizer, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.22:no.5 (2009:Feb.)
  - Item 26: Retiree Organizer, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.22:no.6 (2009:Mar.)
  - Item 27: Retiree Organizer, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.22:no.7 (2009:Apr.)
  - Item 28: Retiree Organizer, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.22:no.8 (2009:May)
  - Item 29: Retiree Organizer, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.22:no.9 (2009:June/July)
  - Item 30: Retiree Organizer, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.23:no.1 (2009:Fall)
  - Item 31: Retiree Organizer, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.23:no.2 (2010:March)
- Box: 2, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: SRP Newslink, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (2003:Oct.)
  - Item 2: SRP Newslink, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (2003:Oct.). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: SRP Newslink, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.2:no.4 (2003:Dec.)
  - Item 4: SRP Newslink, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.2:no.4 (2003:Dec.). Copy 2.
  - Item 5: SRP Newslink, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (2004:Apr.)
  - Item 6: SRP Newslink, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (2004:Apr.). Copy 2.
  - Item 7: SRP Newslink, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (2004:June)
  - Item 8: SRP Newslink, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (2004:June). Copy 2.
  - Item 9: SRP Newslink, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.3:no.3 (2004:Oct.)
  - Item 10: SRP Newslink, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.3:no.3 (2004:Oct.). Copy 2.
  - Item 11: SRP Newslink, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (2005:Jan.)
  - Item 12: SRP Newslink, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (2005:Jan.). Copy 2.
  - Item 13: SRP Newslink, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.2 (2005:Mar.)
  - Item 14: SRP Newslink, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.2 (2005:Mar.). Copy 2.
  - Item 15: SRP Newslink, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.3 (2005:June)
  - Item 16: SRP Newslink, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.3 (2005:June). Copy 2.
  - Item 17: SRP Newslink, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.3 (2005:Fall)
  - Item 18: SRP Newslink, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.3 (2005:Fall). Copy 2.
  - Item 19: SRP Newslink, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.3 (2005:Fall). Copy 3.
  - Item 20: SRP Newslink, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (2008:Fall). Copy 2.
  - Item 21: SRP Newslink, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.7:no.2 (2008:Winter)
  - Item 22: SRP Newslink, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.7:no.2 (2008:Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 23: SRP Newslink, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.7:no.3 (2009:Spring)
  - Item 24: SRP Newslink, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.7:no.3 (2009:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 25: SRP Newslink, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.7:no.4 (2009:Summer)
  - Item 26: SRP Newslink, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.7:no.4 (2009:Summer). Copy 2.
  - Item 27: SRP Newslink, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (2009:Fall)
  - Item 28: SRP Newslink, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (2009:Fall). Copy 2.
  - Item 29: SRP Newslink, 2010; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (2010:Winter)
  - Item 30: SRP Newslink, 2010; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (2010:Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 31: SRP Newslink, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (2002:Spring)
  - Item 32: SRP Newslink, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (2002:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 33: SRP Newslink, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (2002:July)
  - Item 34: SRP Newslink, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (2002:July). Copy 2.
  - Item 35: SRP Newslink, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.3 (2002:Oct.)
  - Item 36: SRP Newslink, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.3 (2002:Oct.). Copy 2.
  - Item 37: SRP Newslink, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.4 (2002:Dec.)
  - Item 38: SRP Newslink, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.4 (2002:Dec.). Copy 2.
  - Item 39: SRP Newslink, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (2003:Feb.)
  - Item 40: SRP Newslink, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (2003:Feb.). Copy 2.
  - Item 41: SRP Newslink, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (2003:June)
  - Item 42: SRP Newslink, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (2003:June). Copy 2.
  - Item 43: SRP Newslink, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 (2005:Winter)
  - Item 44: SRP Newslink, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 (2005:Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 45: SRP Newslink, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 (2005:Winter). Copy 3.
  - Item 46: SRP Newslink, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.5 (2006:Spring)
  - Item 47: SRP Newslink, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.5 (2006:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 48: SRP Newslink, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.5 (2006:Spring). Copy 3.
  - Item 49: SRP Newslink, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.6 (2006:Summer)
  - Item 50: SRP Newslink, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.6 (2006:Summer). Copy 2.
  - Item 51: SRP Newslink, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.6 (2006:Summer). Copy 3.
  - Item 52: SRP Newslink, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (2006:Fall)
  - Item 53: SRP Newslink, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (2006:Fall). Copy 2.
  - Item 54: SRP Newslink, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (2006:Fall). Copy 3.
  - Item 55: SRP Newslink, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (2006:Winter)
  - Item 56: SRP Newslink, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (2006:Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 57: SRP Newslink, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (2006:Winter). Copy 3.
  - Item 58: SRP Newslink, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.5:no.3 (2007:Spring)
  - Item 59: SRP Newslink, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.5:no.3 (2007:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 60: SRP Newslink, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.5:no.3 (2007:Spring). Copy 3.
  - Item 61: SRP Newslink, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (2007:Summer)
  - Item 62: SRP Newslink, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (2007:Summer). Copy 2.
  - Item 63: SRP Newslink, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (2007:Summer). Copy 3.
  - Item 64: SRP Newslink, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.1 (2007:Fall)
  - Item 65: SRP Newslink, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.1 (2007:Fall). Copy 2.
  - Item 66: SRP Newslink, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.2 (2007:Winter)
  - Item 67: SRP Newslink, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.2 (2007:Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 68: SRP Newslink, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.3 (2008:Spring)
  - Item 69: SRP Newslink, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.3 (2008:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 70: SRP Newslink, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 (2008:Summer)
  - Item 71: SRP Newslink, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 (2008:Summer). Copy 2.
  - Item 72: SRP Newslink, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (2008:Fall)
  - Item 73: SRP Newslink, 2010; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.8:no.3 (2010:Spring)
  - Item 74: SRP Newslink, 2010; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.8:no.3 (2010:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 75: SRP Newslink, 2010; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.8:no.4 (2010:Summer)
  - Item 76: SRP Newslink, 2010; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.8:no.4 (2010:Summer). Copy 2.
- Box: 2, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: RA 2005 Program and Awards Book, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: 33rd Annual Representative Assembly (RA), April 7-9, 2005, New York, NY.
  - Item 2: Legislative Program, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Resolutions Proposed for Reaffirmation, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Resolutions Due To Expire in 2006, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Proposed Amendment to the Constitution and Bylaws, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Proposed Amendment to the Constitution and Bylaws, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: 33rd Annual Representative Assembly (RA), April 7-9, 2005, New York, NY. Copy 2.
  - Item 7: Annual Report to NYSUT Delegates Regarding NYSUT Member Benefits and NYSUT Social Services, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Author: Richard C. Iannuzzi
  - Item 8: Annual Report: April 2005, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Author: Ivan Tiger
- Box: 2, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Thomas Y. Hobart, Jr. Commemorative Journal, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: April 2005.
- Advocate, Publication (Box 3)
  - Box: 3, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Advocate, 1990; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Author: NEA-NY (National Education Association of New York)
      Notes: v.16:no.10 (1990:June)
    - Item 2: Advocate, 1990; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Notes: v.17:no.4 (1990:Dec.)
    - Item 3: Advocate, 1991; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Notes: v.17:no.5 (1991:Jan.)
    - Item 4: Advocate, 1991; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Notes: v.17:no.6 (1991:Feb.)
    - Item 5: Advocate, 1991; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Notes: v.17:no.7 (1991:Mar.)
    - Item 6: Advocate, 1991; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Notes: v.17:no.8 (1991:Apr.)
    - Item 7: Advocate, 1991; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Notes: v.17:no.9 (1991:May)
    - Item 8: Advocate, 1991; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Notes: v.17:no.10 (1991:June)
    - Item 9: Advocate, 1991; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Notes: v.17:no.11 (1991:July)
    - Item 10: Advocate, 1990; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Notes: v.16:no.11 (1990:July/Aug.)
    - Item 11: Advocate, 1990; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Notes: v.17:no.1 (1990:Sept.)
    - Item 12: Advocate, 1990; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Notes: v.17:no.2 (1990:Oct.)
    - Item 13: Advocate, 1990; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Notes: v.17:no.3 (1990:Nov.)
  - Box: 3, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Advocate, 1991; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.18:no.1 (1991:Sept.)
    - Item 2: Advocate, 1991; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.18:no.2 (1991:Oct.)
    - Item 3: Advocate, 1991; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.18:no.3 (1991:Nov./Dec.)
    - Item 4: Advocate, 1992; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.18:no.4 (1992:Jan.)
    - Item 5: Advocate, 1992; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.18:no.5 (1992:Feb.)
    - Item 6: Advocate, 1992; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.18:no.6 (1992:Mar.)
    - Item 7: Advocate, 1992; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.18:no.7 (1992:Apr.)
    - Item 8: Advocate, 1992; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.18:no.8 (1992:May)
    - Item 9: Advocate, 1992; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.18:no.9 (1992:June/July)
  - Box: 3, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Advocate, 1992; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.19:no.1 (1992:Sept.)
    - Item 2: Advocate, 1992; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.19:no.2 (1992:Oct.)
    - Item 3: Advocate, 1992; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.19:no.3 (1992:Nov./Dec.)
    - Item 4: Advocate, 1993; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.19:no.4 (1993:Jan.)
    - Item 5: Advocate, 1993; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.19:no.5 (1993:Feb.)
    - Item 6: Advocate, 1993; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.19:no.6 (1993:Mar.)